{
	"inventions":
	[
		{
			"_id":1,
			"Question":"Who invented the BALLPOINT PEN",
			"OptionA":"Biro Brothers",
			"OptionB":"Waterman Brothers",
			"OptionC":"Bicc Brothers",
			"OptionD":"Write Brothers",
			"Answer":"A"
		},
		{
			"_id":2,
			"Question":"What J. B. Dunlop invented",
			"OptionA":"Pneumatic rubber tire",
			"OptionB":"Automobile wheel rim",
			"OptionC":"Rubber boot",
			"OptionD":"Model airplanes",
			"Answer":"A"
		},
		{
			"_id":3,
			"Question":"Who discovered radioactive element radium",
			"OptionA":"Isaac Newton",
			"OptionB":"Albert Einstein",
			"OptionC":"Benjamin Franklin",
			"OptionD":"Marie Curie",
			"Answer":"D"
		},
		{
			"_id":4,
			"Question":"When was barb wire patented",
			"OptionA":"1874",
			"OptionB":"1840",
			"OptionC":"1895",
			"OptionD":"1900",
			"Answer":"A"
		},
		{
			"_id":5,
			"Question":"James Watt invented",
			"OptionA":"Diving bell",
			"OptionB":"Steam boat",
			"OptionC":"Hot air balloon",
			"OptionD":"steam engine",
			"Answer":"D"
		},
		{
			"_id":6,
			"Question":"Who invented Jet Engine",
			"OptionA":"Sir Frank Whittle",
			"OptionB":"Gottlieb Daimler",
			"OptionC":"Roger Bacon",
			"OptionD":"Lewis E. Waterman",
			"Answer":"A"
		},
		{
			"_id":7,
			"Question":"Invention caused many deaths while testing",
			"OptionA":"Dynamite",
			"OptionB":"Ladders",
			"OptionC":"Race cars",
			"OptionD":"Parachute",
			"Answer":"D"
		},
		{
			"_id":8,
			"Question":"Who invented Gunpowder",
			"OptionA":"Sir Frank Whittle",
			"OptionB":"Roger Bacon",
			"OptionC":"Leo H Baekeland",
			"OptionD":"Ferdinand Von",
			"Answer":"B"
		},
		{
			"_id":9,
			"Question":"Benjamin Franklin invented",
			"OptionA":"Bifocal spectacles",
			"OptionB":"Radio",
			"OptionC":"Barometer",
			"OptionD":"Hygrometer",
			"Answer":"A"
		},
		{
			"_id":10,
			"Question":"Joe McVicker invented",
			"OptionA":"Silly Putty",
			"OptionB":"Etch-A-Sketch",
			"OptionC":"Lite-Brite",
			"OptionD":"Play-Doh",
			"Answer":"D"
		},
		{
			"_id":11,
			"Question":"Who invented Gramophone",
			"OptionA":"Michael Faraday",
			"OptionB":"Fahrenheit",
			"OptionC":"Graham Bell",
			"OptionD":"Thomas Alva Edison",
			"Answer":"D"
		},
		{
			"_id":12,
			"Question":"When was the first lawn mower invented",
			"OptionA":"1830",
			"OptionB":"1854",
			"OptionC":"1835",
			"OptionD":"1849",
			"Answer":"A"
		},
		{
			"_id":13,
			"Question":" Physicist responsible for  'Big Bang Theory'",
			"OptionA":"Albert Einstein",
			"OptionB":"Michael Skube",
			"OptionC":"George Gamow",
			"OptionD":"Roger Penrose",
			"Answer":"C"
		},
		{
			"_id":14,
			"Question":"Who invented the fountain pen",
			"OptionA":" Waterman",
			"OptionB":"Sir William Grove",
			"OptionC":"Charles Kettering",
			"OptionD":"George Fountain",
			"Answer":"A"
		},
		{
			"_id":15,
			"Question":"When was the first elevator built",
			"OptionA":"1743",
			"OptionB":"1740",
			"OptionC":"1753",
			"OptionD":"1763",
			"Answer":"A"
		},
		{
			"_id":16,
			"Question":"Enrico Fermi invented",
			"OptionA":"X ray machine",
			"OptionB":"Betatron",
			"OptionC":"Cyclotron",
			"OptionD":"Nuclear reactor",
			"Answer":"D"
		},
		{
			"_id":17,
			"Question":"Thomas Davenport invented",
			"OptionA":"Screw propellor",
			"OptionB":"Electric streetcar",
			"OptionC":"Chesterfield",
			"OptionD":"Sleeping (railway) car",
			"Answer":"B"
		},
		{
			"_id":18,
			"Question":"Elisha Otis invented",
			"OptionA":"Brake used in  elevators",
			"OptionB":"Jet Engine",
			"OptionC":"Turbine",
			"OptionD":"Hydraulic Crane",
			"Answer":"A"
		},
		{
			"_id":19,
			"Question":"Where was the yo-yo invented",
			"OptionA":"France",
			"OptionB":"United States",
			"OptionC":"Philippines",
			"OptionD":"England",
			"Answer":"C"
		},
		{
			"_id":20,
			"Question":"
When were blue jeans invented",
			"OptionA":"1900s",
			"OptionB":"1860s",
			"OptionC":"1870s",
			"OptionD":"1850s",
			"Answer":"D"
		},
		{
			"_id":21,
			"Question":"Who invented Electric Generator",
			"OptionA":"Alfred B. Nobel",
			"OptionB":" Graham Bell",
			"OptionC":"Michael Faraday",
			"OptionD":"Alva Edison",
			"Answer":"C"
		},
		{
			"_id":22,
			"Question":"Transistor was invented in",
			"OptionA":"1940s",
			"OptionB":"1960s",
			"OptionC":"1950s",
			"OptionD":"1980s",
			"Answer":"A"
		},
		{
			"_id":23,
			"Question":"Karl Benz invented",
			"OptionA":"Gasoline powered automobile",
			"OptionB":"Streetcar",
			"OptionC":"Glider",
			"OptionD":"Steam turbine",
			"Answer":"A"
		},
		{
			"_id":24,
			"Question":"Bar code scanners were invented in",
			"OptionA":"1940s",
			"OptionB":"1950s",
			"OptionC":"1970s",
			"OptionD":"1960s",
			"Answer":"C"
		},
		{
			"_id":25,
			"Question":"Who invented Dynamite",
			"OptionA":"Alexander Graham Bell",
			"OptionB":"Benjamin Franklin",
			"OptionC":"Thomas Alva Edison",
			"OptionD":"Alfred B. Nobel",
			"Answer":"D"
		},
	]
}